CTHub
CtMe
CTiD
CT Finder
CT Pair
Something CT
Creative Tech Space
CT Space
loc. CT
Locate CT
CT City
City CT
CommuniTy
CommuniTech
CT Spot
Creative Compass
CT Labs
CTech
CreaTech
Hire CT
Direct CT
InvenT


(name) is the spot for Creative Technologists to discover a company that fits them and vice versa. We pair with forward thinking companies that seek the specialized skills a CT possesses. We know that every CT is different and some companies aren't ready for a CT.  We only want to pair you with companies that desire to grow by embracing a new breed of Creatives. 


?
company or agency? Might have more than just agencies looking for CTs


Games

1. Program Knowledge
Have icons from common programs ie. Adobe. They could drag and drop them into an area such as a tool belt. They could plot them on a graph to see which one they are strongest at.Could possibly tie into Linkedin endorsements.

2. Work Experience
Maybe gets pulled in from Linkedin, but if not.
Have a database that has icons of companies (like Facebook does) and have the user plot on the icons in a timeline of where and when they worked at a location.

3. Work they like
Have a flash card game of work form participating agencies. The cards flash up for a predetermined time and the user picks the one they like better. Tells us what agency best fits them determined by the work.
